specific
stocks and see
how the market can set its price in the market. So let's start.
As we discussed,
if the market moves above the 2000 mark here,
we will see
a consolidation at expiry. Now we can take
a short cut here
because the price here is a little below the 2000 mark. We
can see Bank Nifty at 3608.
Today we saw Baikunthi and the 2000 mark
with the 2000 mark. So, considering this,
you will see the market burning fat here. So let's
see that this is the
syllabus. By doing this, we will do Kanchana for our feet.
First and last, Punit
Continuity, for these days, there is a
setting show here, but
later we can see a short covering clearly
here. So today or
above 2008, we saw a question which is
currently being considered.
From the open interest here, it is clear that this can
act as the strongest support
because  In this, the bank guarantee is a good
use, you can see the writing clean here,
at these higher levels there is a
little bit of push typing here, so even if
you will see some profit booking tomorrow,
then also we can smoothen it further by crossing an Indra Mani Kaul on the zoo,
because if the price is
above its seventh tip in America, then at least
we will cut it to see
whether it activates this layer or
not and after this, looking at a style, you
can apply a strong Indra Mani Kaul here, this time Bank
Nifty can come here and mostly 9 inches
with a week, if seen, then
after today's open,
we can see a strong recovery in this last three and a half channel,
suicide right now at
3632, if you get a copy in it, then
you can buy such an option brother, a British in it
and that too Indra Mani, which you
will use here on the open interest, so guys,
if seen then  There is
a call writing at 3692 but apart from the below right now,
it is from 36500 to 30 seconds
here we
can see the chords being estimated at which level I am
tight so tomorrow
on touching 3803 you can use
a pin Ramnik Kaur powder here at 5065
so let's see which are those
stocks which we will pit for ourselves tomorrow, the
first topic which is small is that it has been
moving ahead for the last few days with a strong volume and here we are talking about
that task like
tight hug on project stocks, consolidate on the level of Yagya Stock Fund,
so if it settles
above 12105 only tomorrow, we can settle at least nine
more, then you
can chase the target from 24-12-2012,
stoploss we need a surplus inches of ₹10,
if we want to scalp in it  If we
talk further after this, then the second
stock is Kotak Mahindra Guy, which today
due to its volume pickup, has crossed above its
previous resistance of parentheses,
which asked its question
at 1431, we are also one last time if that is and the
last hour canal is crossed above DI here,
so Guys, if tomorrow the stock can
try the lottery at the above mentioned time of 835
and on its basis our target will be
around 10 2018, just stop we
can withdraw cash, now the level of 2810 phone
in CAD, if we want to dominate here, then
and after this the
third point is India and this also today
due to a strong breakout, we have to take our day,
however, on the words, here, asparagus ghee,
this center after 230 and 130,
becomes quite our decoration because of this,
one thing is that tomorrow in the expiry,
we will get to see a little bit of it,
they have it, if it goes above 400, you  If you
look at the batter then you
can get at least 528 equities and cut off the head of a soldier.
After this, the next stock is this thing
sir, after consolidating for the last few days,
today we see a strong
breakout in it for Twenty20 above it,
so guide next because the
stock has been
sent to our committee. Sources, if you see an
alert of colorful soil here at the
time of opening against Ray, then you can get
at least ₹50 Kartik, where can I get a tablet in it,
so come on, that's all for today
in this video, if you have not yet done
our oil control, what is pulling and
details, you will get it in the description below,
friend, want to get more excuses,
update on future and option trace, see
here, disco group link, which has
interdiction club and don't want to join
award model portfolio, see interested to join them from
depression sweater next
flight's watching dad I miss you in a
lift jhal jhal jhal jhal jhal jhal jhal jhal jhal jhal jhal jhal
Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal
Ki A
[Music]